[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
I will.
Thank you.
Pack all your things.
Why did you suddenly disappear?
I only wounded her.
You know you only made her angrier.
Your mother was right.
Don't worry.
I'll handle him.
Are you sure?
Like I said,
and I'm the only one who can deal with it.
So, I'm the one who'll fix it.
It's pretty obvious the Castellanis are hunting him down.
if he manages to escape with his partner.
That might be difficult.
Those bastards are a little too war-hungry.
This is a perfect opportunity
if the Castellanis will listen to Chiara.
what's your plan?
Fix the problem
without making noise.
Why haven't we heard anything on comms?
What's happening to Alex?
Lost radio power.
But I don't have a Schengen visa.
It takes forever to process, and we don't have the budget!
We have Mikoy's asset there
who can help them.
Looks like we can't get out of here.
Because they control this area.
Even the local police.
We still have one option.
Don't tell me you're counting on your informant again?
He still hasn't let me down up to now, Alex.
You really trust that informant that much.
Well, no matter how good he is,
there's no getting past the Castellanis.
Because this isn't just their territory,
it's their kingdom.
He's here.
You?
Come here.
You've got some nerve!
-What is he doing here? -Alex, relax!
He's just paying for his sins.
You have a strong grip, sis.
Rahmboy.
The area is on lockdown.
No one's getting out.
There's money and gold on your heads.
So everyone around here
is looking for the two of you.
So basically, you can't help us?
I didn't say that.
Of course I can help you.
Come on, you know me.
I owe him big time.
So what?
Where are you planning to hide us?
Some kind of animal cage,
or maybe a sewer?
Worse than an animal cage or a sewer, bro.
Where?
Wait.
Why here?
Have you lost your mind?
Do you want us to get killed?
Believe it or not, Sister Alex,
How can you say that?
And a five-star place
Because if anything bad happens to the guests
in a high-end place like that…
it would be bad for Italy's reputation.
The Castellanis won't make a move inside that five-star hotel.
You know you only made her angrier.
How long are we staying here?
look’s like we are not in Castellani’s radar now.
He spread a rumor about us escaping.
Seems like that asset of yours is trustworthy.
Wait, I thought we were staying here?
He'll arrange transportation for us to leave Italy.
Sorry about what?
I'm sorry you weren't able to do what you were supposed to do here.
And now, it looks like Chiara is back in Prague.
I have the rest of my life to hunt her down
and make her pay for what she did.
This is how big a ten-peso pandesal is?
What is this?
That's fresh from the oven, sweetheart.
I can smell that.
Why are you smiling like that?
So damn wide.
It just reminded me of Italy.
Do you know the best time in Italy is in the morning?
Because that's when the city smells like newly baked bread.
Let's go there, sweetheart!
Then, let's see if they smell even better
than the ten-peso pandesal
from Tonyo's Bakery!
I think this still smells better.
Looks like you don't have a gun with you now, sweetheart.
Because if you did, I'd be dead by now, right?
Are you sure?
But it won't be quick.
You won't make it easy.
You know and I know
that I can be faster than that.
All I need is two minutes.
Your jokes with the double meanings.
All I'm saying is
we have another time for this.
For now, you have to go back to Alex.
Why? Huh?
What is it this time?!
What did you do?
HOTEL ELISEO
Come on!
Let's go.
Please guide me,
especially Chiara.
Don't let her heart influence her mind.
This is what was meant to be. It must be fulfilled.
Did something happen?
Who? Mother Mary?
Chiara.
What?
What happened?
I got close to her.
Are you saying she saved me?
I don't know.
All I know is,
she would've done it already.
What did she say?
She said we'll face each other.
Looks like she's coming back to the Philippines.
How did that happen?
All this time, there were eyes watching our every move.
So you already know Mikoy's asset?
Who is he?
More importantly, can we trust him?
At least we're sure of his pronouns.
But I have to respect Mikoy's request
not to reveal his asset's identity.
He doesn't want to violate bro code!
And as for the question of whether we can trust him,
he saved us.
He had every opportunity
to betray us and turn us over to Chiara and the Concordat,
for his own advantage,
but he still chose to help us.
Mikoy's asset can be trusted.
Do you have anything else to say?
But she didn't.
Despite knowing we were there and Mikoy was there to assassinate her.
Or maybe
There are a lot of reasons
why Chiara didn't let you die.
she didn't let me die because…
Where's Mikoy?
What's that?
I still brought you guys some pasalubong!
This is a promise.
-I want the wafer. -Sweet!
-There, and then… -This is wafer.
Perfume!
-Hey! -Hey!
Stateside, from Italy!
-That's right. -Spray it in your mouth,
-so it'll smell nice for once. -Captain Pepe.
Alcologne.
-It tastes like alcohol too! -No!
It's just perfume.
-This one's for you. -Try it.
My most favorite sibling!
-I don't have… -This is great.
Thank you, bro!
-Seems you have favoritism. -Something to bring to school.
And of course, we must not forget my dearest mother, right?
-There. -Of course.
Mom!
There are some snacks in there, Mom.
Those have a lot of sugar, Tess.
They're sweet.
Son.
Can I talk to you?
Yes, Mom.
Here’s my gift. Open it.
Saikyu.
Shaku.
if you want to slice Mikoy’s neck.
You know why I want to eliminate him.
After what happened in Italy,
we can't underestimate him anymore.
And, yes, he failed
when he tried to assassinate you.
But that doesn't mean
he won't try again.
Maybe next time,
and he'll finally
take you down.
Are you underestimating me?
That's not what I meant.
But I think
you have another reason
why you want Mikoy dead so badly.
There's another reason why you want Mikoy gone so badly.
Because you know that
if there's one person in this world I'd listen to, it's him.
I'm sorry, Dad.
This is the only way I know.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make whoever did this pay.
You're going to have Chiara killed?
I know you can't bring yourself to kill Chiara.
I already have another option.
For sure they won't survive tonight.
I'm not your enemy.
What's going on here?
Lower your guns.
He's Mikoy's secret asset.
What is he doing here?
Looks like my sweetheart still hasn't changed at all.